# SHANE CHRISTIE

### WEBSITE DEVELOPER



786-618-2301

ShaneAzaniaChristie@gmail.com

West Palm Beach, Fl

ShaneAzania.com GitHub.com/ShaneAzania

## PROFILE

A self motivated web developer with experience in Front End and Back End Development frameworks, strong creative and problem solving skills, team player mentality, an eye for detail, with the will and urge to learn any and everything needed to become a great team asset.

## SKILLS

- Front End Web Development
- · React, Redux, & Context
- · Javascript, CSS, HTML
- SASS
- Python, Django, and Flask
- MySQL
- Firebase (noSQL)
- Git Hub
- Web Master

# EDUCATION

# SOFTWARE ENGINEERING BOOTCAMP

CODING DOJO

2022

## **BACHELOR OF BUSINESS**

FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY 2020 - 2022

# EXPERIENCE

#### WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER

seVIIn Threads | https://seviin-threads.netlify.app/

2022 - Present

- E-commerce Full Stack Developer
- Utilizing React, Redux, JavaScript, Google Firebase (noSQL),
  Google User Authentication, Styled javascript components, SASS and Bootstrap

#### INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

PALM BEACH COUNTY SCHOOL DISTRICT

2022 - Present

- Technology troubleshooting, problem solving, management and installation
- Active Directory administrative duties
- Student management

### WEB MASTER AND BUILDER

CIIITY MEDIA | ciiitymedia.com

2017 - 2022

- Increased online interactions and media presence by building website on Wordpress for CMS
- Broadened the reach and ease of access for online customers, and increasing sales by including e-commerce functionality and social multi platform store integration